hermo.my 2013-06-18

# Help Center — Welcome to Hermo

At  **hermo.my** , we take your privacy seriously! Please read this  **Statement of Privacy**  to be more aware about our policy on collecting, using and disclosing personal information.  **hermo.com.my**  occasionally update this  **Statement of Privacy**  to reflect company and user feedback. We encourage you to review this Statement periodically to be informed of how we are protecting your personal information. 

**_Privacy policy_**

**hermo.my**  treats personal information, such as your name, email address or telephone number as important privacy. We promise your personal information will not be disclosed to third party. We will not use or sell your personal information to third party unless:

1) Users agreed to share with third party;

2) Users make known to pubilc of their personal information in selves-willingness in in order to enjoy products or services;

3) Violations of  **hermo.my's**  Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by the law.

**_Instructions for use_**

**hermo.my**  is committed to protect the security of your personal information. We use password setting up by user to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Users are fully responsible for protecting their password. If users are using public computer, please logout before leaving to prevent disclosure of personal information.

**_Terms_**

By using this site and providing information as a registered user, you are in agreement with our privacy policy. We are not responsible for the breach of our privacy statements or other content on websites outside the  **hermo.my**  domain name.
